Guide to the Communications Workers of America Records Addendum WAG.124.001
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series I: Files of the Presidents Office, 1970-1998.
  - Subseries I:C: General Files, 1970-1996.
    - Organizations: Council on Competitiveness, 1988 (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Organizations: Economic Policy Council of the United Nations Association, Jan 1989-Jul 1989 (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - Organizations: Economic Policy Council of the United Nations Association, Aug 1989-Dec 1989 (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - Organizations: Economic Policy Council of the United Nations Association, 1990 (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - Organizations: Economic Policy Institute, 1989 (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - Organizations: Economic Policy Institute, 1990 (Box 45, Folder 10)
    - Organizations: Export-Import Bank of the United States, 1989-1990 (Box 45, Folder 11)
    - Organizations: General, 1985 (Box 45, Folder 12)
    - Organizations: General, Jan 1986 (Box 45, Folder 13)
    - Organizations: General, Feb 1986-Mar 1986 (Box 45, Folder 14)
    - Organizations: General, Apr 1986 (Box 45, Folder 15)
    - Organizations: General, May 1986 (Box 45, Folder 16)
    - Organizations: General, Jun 1986 (Box 45, Folder 17)
    - Organizations: General, Jul 1986 (Box 45, Folder 18)
    - Organizations: General, Aug 1986 (Box 45, Folder 19)
    - Organizations: General, Sep 1986 (Box 45, Folder 20)
    - Organizations: General, Oct 1986 (Box 45, Folder 21)
    - Organizations: General, Nov 1986-Dec 1986 (Box 45, Folder 22)
    - Organizations: General, Jan 1987-Feb 1987 (Box 45, Folder 23)
    - Organizations: General, Mar 1987 (Box 45, Folder 24)
    - Organizations: General, Apr 1987-May 1987 (Box 45, Folder 25)
    - Organizations: General, Jun 1987-Jul 1987 (Box 45, Folder 26)
    - Organizations: General, Aug 1987 (Box 45, Folder 27)
    - Organizations: General, Sep 1987 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Organizations: General, Oct 1987 (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - Organizations: General, Nov 1987 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - Organizations: General, Dec 1987 (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Organizations: General, Feb 1988 (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - Organizations: General, Mar 1988 (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - Organizations: General, Apr 1988 (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - Organizations: General, May 1988 (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - Organizations: General, Jun 1988-Jul 1988 (Box 46, Folder 9)
    - Organizations: General, Aug 1988 (Box 46, Folder 10)
    - Organizations: General, Sep 1988-Oct 1988 (Box 46, Folder 11)
    - Organizations: General, Nov 1988 (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - Organizations: General, Dec 1988 (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Organizations: General, Jan 1989-Mar 1989 (Box 46, Folder 14)
    - Organizations: General, Apr 1989-Jun 1989 (Box 46, Folder 15)
    - Organizations: General, Jul 1989 (Box 46, Folder 16)
    - Organizations: General, Aug 1989-Dec 1989 (Box 46, Folder 17)
    - Organizations: General, 1990 (Box 46, Folder 18)
    - Organizations: General, 1991 (Box 46, Folder 19)
    - Organizations: General, 1992 (Box 46, Folder 20)
    - Organizations: General, 1993 (Box 46, Folder 21)
    - Organizations: General, 1994-1995 (Box 46, Folder 22)
    - Organizations: Jewish, 1986 (Box 46, Folder 23)
    - Organizations: Jewish, Jan 1987-Jun 1987 (Box 46, Folder 24)
    - Organizations: Jewish, Jul 1987-Dec 1987 (Box 46, Folder 25)
    - Organizations: Jewish, 1989 (Box 46, Folder 26)
    - Organizations: Jewish, Bahr Dinner, Dec 1989 (Box 46, Folder 27)
    - Organizations: Jewish, 1990 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Organizations: Jewish, 1991 (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Organizations: Jewish, 1992-1993 (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - Organizations: Jewish, 1994-1995 (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - Organizations: Jewish, 1996 (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - Organizations: March of Dimes, Morton Bahr Dinner, 1986 (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - Organizations: National Democratic Institute for International Affairs, 1986 (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - Organizations: National Urban League, 1986 (Box 47, Folder 8)
    - Organizations: Points of Light Foundation, 1992-1993 (Box 47, Folder 9)
    - Organizations: Points of Light Foundation, 1994-1995 (Box 47, Folder 10)
    - Organizations: Randolph Institute, 1986 (Box 47, Folder 11)
    - Organizations: Randolph Institute, 1987 (Box 47, Folder 12)
    - Organizations: Randolph Institute, 1991 (Box 47, Folder 13)
    - Organizations: Red Cross, 1987 (Box 47, Folder 14)
    - Organizations: Stony Brook Center for Labor-Management Studies, 1990 (Box 47, Folder 15)
    - Organizations: Work in America Institute, 1989 (Box 47, Folder 16)
    - Organizations: Work in America Institute, 1990 (Box 47, Folder 17)
    - Organizing, ca.1981-1982 (Box 47, Folder 18)
    - Organizing, Jan 1986 (Box 47, Folder 19)
    - Organizing, Feb 1986 (Box 47, Folder 20)
    - Organizing, Mar 1986 (Box 47, Folder 21)
    - Organizing, Apr 1986 (Box 47, Folder 22)
    - Organizing, May 1986 (Box 47, Folder 23)
    - Organizing, Jun 1986 (Box 47, Folder 24)
    - Organizing, Jul 1986 (Box 47, Folder 25)
    - Organizing, Aug 1986 (Box 47, Folder 26)
    - Organizing, Sep 1986 (Box 47, Folder 27)
    - Organizing, Oct 1986 (Box 47, Folder 28)
    - Organizing, Nov 1986 (Box 47, Folder 29)
    - Organizing, Dec 1986 (Box 47, Folder 30)
    - Organizing, Jan 1987 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Organizing, Feb 1987 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Organizing, Mar 2, 1987-Mar 20, 1987 (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Organizing, Mar 23, 1987-Mar 31, 1987 (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Organizing, Apr 1987 (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - Organizing, May 1987 (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - Organizing, Jun 1987 (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - Organizing, Jul 1987 (Box 48, Folder 8)
    - Organizing, Aug 1987 (Box 48, Folder 9)
    - Organizing, Oct 1987 (Box 48, Folder 10)
    - Organizing, Nov 1987 (Box 48, Folder 11)
    - Organizing, Dec 1987 (Box 48, Folder 12)
    - Organizing, Jan 1988 (Box 48, Folder 13)
    - Organizing, Feb 1988 (Box 48, Folder 14)
    - Organizing, Mar 1988 (Box 48, Folder 15)
    - Organizing, Apr 1988 (Box 48, Folder 16)
    - Organizing, May 1988 (Box 48, Folder 17)
    - Organizing, Jun 1988 (Box 48, Folder 18)
    - Organizing, Jul 1988 (Box 48, Folder 19)
    - Organizing, Aug 1988-Sep 1988 (Box 48, Folder 20)
    - Organizing, Oct 1988 (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Organizing, Nov 1988 (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - Organizing, Dec 1988 (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Organizing, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - Organizing, 1994-1995 (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - Organizing, 1996 (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - Organizing: District 1, 1986 (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - Organizing: District 1, 1987-1988 (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - Organizing: District 1, 1992-1995 (Box 49, Folder 9)
    - Organizing: District 2, 1986 (Box 49, Folder 10)
    - Organizing: District 2, 1987-1988 (Box 49, Folder 11)
    - Organizing: District 3, 1986 (Box 49, Folder 12)
    - Organizing: District 3, 1987-1988 (Box 49, Folder 13)
    - Organizing: District 4, 1986 (Box 49, Folder 14)
    - Organizing: District 4, 1987-1988 (Box 49, Folder 15)
    - Organizing: District 5, 1986 (Box 49, Folder 16)
    - Organizing: District 6, 1986 (Box 49, Folder 17)
    - Organizing: District 6, 1987-1988 (Box 49, Folder 18)
    - Organizing: District 7, 1986 (Box 49, Folder 19)
    - Organizing: District 7, 1987-1988 (Box 49, Folder 20)
    - Organizing: District 8, 1987 (Box 49, Folder 21)
    - Organizing: District 9, 1986, 1988 (Box 49, Folder 22)
    - Organizing: District 10, 1986 (Box 49, Folder 23)
    - Organizing: District 11, 1986 (Box 49, Folder 24)
    - Organizing: District 12, 1986 (Box 49, Folder 25)
    - Organizing: District 13, 1986-1988 (Box 49, Folder 26)
    - Organizing: Membership Development, 1986 (Box 49, Folder 27)
    - Organizing: Membership Development, 1987 (Box 49, Folder 28)
    - Organizing: Membership Development, 1988 (Box 49, Folder 29)
    - Pediatric AIDS Foundation, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 30)
    - Political: CWA COPE, Jan 1, 1986-Jan 17, 1986 (Box 49, Folder 31)
    - Political: CWA COPE, Jan 18, 1986-Jan 31, 1986 (Box 49, Folder 32)
    - Political: CWA COPE, Feb 1986 (Box 49, Folder 33)
    - Political: CWA COPE, Mar 1, 1986-Mar 13, 1986 (Box 49, Folder 34)
    - Political: CWA COPE, Mar 14, 1986-Mar 31, 1986 (Box 49, Folder 35)
    - Political: CWA COPE, Apr 1, 1986-Apr 14, 1986 (Box 49, Folder 36)
    - Political: CWA COPE, Apr 15, 1986-Apr 30, 1986 (Box 49, Folder 37)
    - Political: CWA COPE, May 1986 (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Political: CWA COPE, Jun 1986 (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - Political: CWA COPE, Jul 1986 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Political: CWA COPE, Aug 1, 1986-Aug 15, 1986 (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - Political: CWA COPE, Aug 16, 1986-Aug 31, 1986 (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - Political: CWA COPE, Sep 1, 1986-Sep 14, 1986 (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - Political: CWA COPE, Sep 15, 1986-Sep 30, 1986 (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - Political: CWA COPE, Oct 1, 1986-Oct 19, 1986 (Box 50, Folder 8)
    - Political: CWA COPE, Oct 20, 1986-Oct 31, 1986 (Box 50, Folder 9)
    - Political: CWA COPE, Nov 1986 (Box 50, Folder 10)
    - Political: CWA COPE, Dec 1986 (Box 50, Folder 11)
    - Political: CWA COPE, Jan 1987 (Box 50, Folder 12)
    - Political: CWA COPE, Feb 1987 (Box 50, Folder 13)
    - Political: CWA COPE, Mar 1987 (Box 50, Folder 14)
    - Political: CWA COPE, Apr 1987 (Box 50, Folder 15)
    - Political: CWA COPE, May 1987 (Box 50, Folder 16)
    - Political: CWA COPE, Jun 1987 (Box 50, Folder 17)
    - Political: CWA COPE, Jul 1987 (Box 50, Folder 18)
    - Political: CWA COPE, Aug 1987 (Box 50, Folder 19)
    - Political: CWA COPE, Sep 1987 (Box 50, Folder 20)
    - Political: CWA COPE, Oct 1, 1987-Oct 18, 1987 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Political: CWA COPE, Oct 19, 1987-Oct 31, 1987 (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Political: CWA COPE, Nov 1, 1987-Nov 16, 1987 (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Political: CWA COPE, Nov 17, 1987-Nov 30, 1987 (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - Political: CWA COPE, Dec 1987 (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - Political: CWA COPE, Jan 1988 (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - Political: CWA COPE, Feb 1988 (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - Political: CWA COPE, Mar 1, 1988-Mar 16, 1988 (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - Political: CWA COPE, Mar 17, 1988-Mar 31, 1988 (Box 51, Folder 9)
    - Political: CWA COPE, Apr 1988 (Box 51, Folder 10)
    - Political: CWA COPE, May 1988 (Box 51, Folder 11)
    - Political: CWA COPE, Jun 1988 (Box 51, Folder 12)
    - Political: CWA COPE, Jul 1988 (Box 51, Folder 13)
    - Political: CWA COPE, Aug 1988 (Box 51, Folder 14)
    - Political: CWA COPE, Sep 1988 (Box 51, Folder 15)
    - Political: CWA COPE, Oct 1, 1988-Oct 20, 1988 (Box 51, Folder 16)
    - Political: CWA COPE, Oct 21, 1988-Oct 31, 1988 (Box 51, Folder 17)
    - Political: CWA COPE, Nov 1988 (Box 51, Folder 18)
    - Political: CWA COPE, Dec 1988 (Box 51, Folder 19)
    - Political: Correspondence, Jan 1986-May 1986 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Political: Correspondence, Jun 1986-Aug 1986 (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - Political: Correspondence, Sep 1986-Oct 1986 (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - Political: Correspondence, Nov 1986-Dec 1986 (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Political: Correspondence, Jan 1987-May 1987 (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Political: Correspondence, Jun 1987-Aug 1987 (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - Political: Correspondence, Sep 1987-Dec 1987 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Political: Correspondence, Jan 1988-Feb 1988 (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - Political: Correspondence, Mar 1988-May 1988 (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - Political: Correspondence, Jun 1988-Aug 1988 (Box 52, Folder 10)
    - Political: Correspondence, Sep 1988-Dec 1988 (Box 52, Folder 11)
    - Political: Correspondence, 1990-1991 (Box 52, Folder 12)
    - Political: Correspondence, Jan 1995-May 1995 (Box 52, Folder 13)
    - Political: Correspondence, Jun 1995-Sep 1995 (Box 52, Folder 14)
    - Political: Correspondence, Oct 1995-Dec 1995 (Box 52, Folder 15)
    - Political: Correspondence, Jan 1996-Apr 1996 (Box 52, Folder 16)
    - Political: Correspondence (CWA's Demand and Return System), 1987 (Box 52, Folder 17)
    - Political: Correspondence-Political Mailing I: Member Responses, Jan 1995-Apr 1995 (Box 52, Folder 18)
    - Political: Correspondence-Political Mailing I: Member Responses, May 1995 (Box 52, Folder 19)
    - Political: Correspondence-Political Mailing I: Member's Response, Jun 1995 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Political: Correspondence-Political Mailing I: Member's Response, Jul 1995-Oct 1995 (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - Political: Correspondence-Political Mailing I: Member's Response, Nov 1995-Dec 1995 (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - Political: Democratic National Committee, 1986-1987 (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - Political: Democratic National Committee, Jan 1988-Aug 1988 (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - Political: Democratic National Committee, Sep 1988-Dec 1988 (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - Political: Democratic National Committee, 1991 (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - Political: Democratic National Committee, 1995 (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - Political: Democratic National Convention, 1988 (Box 53, Folder 9)
    - Political: Dues Rebates, 1987 (Box 53, Folder 10)
    - Political: Democratic Party, 1987-1988 (Box 53, Folder 11)
    - Political: Dukakis Campaign, Sep 1988 (Box 53, Folder 12)
    - Political: Dukakis Campaign, Oct 1988 (Box 53, Folder 13)
    - Political: Local 1000-1031 Dues Rebates, 1986 (Box 53, Folder 14)
    - Political: Local 1032 Dues Rebates, A-K, 1986 (Box 53, Folder 15)
    - Political: Local 1032 Dues Rebates, L-Z, 1986 (Box 53, Folder 16)
    - Political: Local 1033 Dues Rebates, A-D, 1986 (Box 53, Folder 17)
    - Political: Local 1033 Dues Rebates, E-M, 1986 (Box 53, Folder 18)
    - Political: Local 1033 Dues Rebates, N-Z, 1986 (Box 53, Folder 19)
    - Political: Local 1034 Dues Rebates, A-C, 1986 (Box 53, Folder 20)
    - Political: Local 1034 Dues Rebates, D-F, 1986 (Box 53, Folder 21)
    - Political: Local 1034 Dues Rebates, G-K, 1986 (Box 53, Folder 22)
    - Political: Local 1034 Dues Rebates, L-P, 1986 (Box 53, Folder 23)
    - Political: Local 1034 Dues Rebates, R-Z, 1986 (Box 53, Folder 24)
    - Political: Local 1037 Dues Rebates, 1986 (Box 53, Folder 25)
    - Political: Local 1038 Dues Rebates, 1986 (Box 53, Folder 26)
    - Political: Local 1039 Dues Rebates, A-K, 1986 (Box 53, Folder 27)
    - Political: Local 1039 Dues Rebates, L-Y, 1986 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Political: Local 10409 Dues Rebates, 1986 (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Political: Local 1060-1082 Dues Rebates, 1986 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Political: Local 1101-1141 Dues Rebates, 1986 (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Political: Local 1150-1180 Dues Rebates, 1986 (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - Political: Local 1250 Dues Rebates, 1986 (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - Political: Local 1366 Dues Rebates, 1986 (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - Political: Local 2100 Dues Rebates, 1986 (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - Political: Local 2101 Dues Rebates, A-K, 1986 (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - Political: Local 2101 Dues Rebates, L-Q, 1986 (Box 54, Folder 10)
    - Political: Local 2101 Dues Rebates, R-Z, 1986 (Box 54, Folder 11)
    - Political: Local 2104-2110 Dues Rebates, 1986 (Box 54, Folder 12)
    - Political: Local 2150 Dues Rebates, 1986 (Box 54, Folder 13)
    - Political: Local 2336 Dues Rebates, 1986 (Box 54, Folder 14)
    - Political: Local 3112-3615 Dues Rebates, 1986 (Box 54, Folder 15)
    - Political: Local 4001-4100 Dues Rebates, 1986 (Box 54, Folder 16)
    - Political: Local 4309 Dues Rebates, A-K, 1986 (Box 54, Folder 17)
    - Political: Local 4309 Dues Rebates, L-Z, 1986 (Box 54, Folder 18)
    - Political: Local 4310-4311 Dues Rebates, 1986 (Box 54, Folder 19)
    - Political: Local 4340 Dues Rebates, A-G, 1986 (Box 54, Folder 20)
    - Political: Local 4340 Dues Rebates, H-L, 1986 (Box 54, Folder 21)
    - Political: Local 4340 Dues Rebates, M-Z, 1986 (Box 54, Folder 22)
    - Political: Local 4351-4501 Dues Rebates\, 1986 (Box 54, Folder 23)
    - Political: Local 5002-5540 Dues Rebates, 1986 (Box 54, Folder 24)
    - Political: Local 5521-5818 Dues Rebates, 1986 (Box 54, Folder 25)
    - Political: Local 5900 Dues Rebates, 1986 (Box 54, Folder 26)
    - Political: Local 6012-6372 Dues Rebates, 1986 (Box 54, Folder 27)
    - Political: Local 6450 Dues Rebates, 1986 (Box 54, Folder 28)
    - Political: Local 7150-7901 Dues Rebates, 1986 (Box 54, Folder 29)
    - Political: Local 8103-8150 Dues Rebates, 1986 (Box 54, Folder 30)
    - Political: Local 8407-8408 Dues Rebates, 1986 (Box 54, Folder 31)
    - Political: Local 8412 Dues Rebates, A-G, 1986 (Box 54, Folder 32)
    - Political: Local 8412 Dues Rebates, H-M, 1986 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Political: Local 8412 Dues Rebates, N-W, 1986 (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Political: Local 8417-8611 Dues Rebates, 1986 (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - Political: Local 9102-9118 Dues Rebates, 1986 (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - Political: Local 9201 Dues Rebates, 1986 (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - Political: Local 9205-9206 Dues Rebates, 1986 (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - Political: Local 9402-9409 Dues Rebates, 1986 (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - Political: Local 9410 Dues Rebates, 1986 (Box 55, Folder 8)
    - Political: Local 9412-9416 Dues Rebates, 1986 (Box 55, Folder 9)
    - Political: Local 9417-9490 Dues Rebates, 1986 (Box 55, Folder 10)
    - Political: Local 10402-10950 Dues Rebates, 1986 (Box 55, Folder 11)
    - Political: Local 11500 Dues Rebates, 1986 (Box 55, Folder 12)
    - Political: Local 11502-11503 Dues Rebates, 1986 (Box 55, Folder 13)
    - Political: Local 11505-11510 Dues Rebates, 1986 (Box 55, Folder 14)
    - Political: Local 11511-11513 Dues Rebates, 1986 (Box 55, Folder 15)
    - Political: Local 11550-11590 Dues Rebates, 1986 (Box 55, Folder 16)
    - Political: Local 12150-12171 Dues Rebates, 1986 (Box 55, Folder 17)
    - Political: Local 13000-13552 Dues Rebates, 1986 (Box 55, Folder 18)
    - Political: National Democratic Institute for International Affairs, 1987-1988 (Box 55, Folder 19)
    - Political: National Elections, 1992 (Box 55, Folder 20)
    - Political: Polls, 1987 (Box 55, Folder 21)
    - Political: President's Committee on Employment of the Handicapped, 1993 (Box 55, Folder 22)
    - Political: Presidential Election, 1988 (Box 55, Folder 23)
    - Political: Republican Party, 1987 (Box 55, Folder 24)
    - Printing, Publishing, and Media Workers Sector (PPMWS), Jan 1989-Mar 1989 (Box 55, Folder 25)
    - PPMWS, Apr 1989-May 1989 (Box 55, Folder 26)
    - PPMWS, May 1989-Jul 1989 (Box 55, Folder 27)
    - PPMWS, Aug 1989-Oct 1989 (Box 55, Folder 28)
    - PPMWS, Nov 1989-Dec 1989 (Box 55, Folder 29)
    - PPMWS, Jan 1990-Apr 1990 (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - PPMWS, May 1990-Aug 1990 (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - PPMWS, Sep 1990-Dec 1990 (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - Privatization, 1994 (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - PT Phone Home-Local 1120, 1993 (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - Public Relations, Jan 1986 (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - Public Relations, Jan 1986 (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - Public Relations, Feb 1, 1986-Feb 12, 1986 (Box 56, Folder 8)
    - Public Relations, Feb 13, 1986-Feb 28, 1986 (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - Public Relations, Mar 1, 1986-Mar 14, 1986 (Box 56, Folder 10)
    - Public Relations, Mar 15, 1986-Mar 31, 1986 (Box 56, Folder 11)
    - Public Relations, Apr 1986 (Box 56, Folder 12)
    - Public Relations, Jun 1986-Jul 1986 (Box 56, Folder 13)
    - Public Relations, Aug 1986 (Box 56, Folder 14)
    - Public Relations, Sep 1986-Oct 1986 (Box 56, Folder 15)
    - Public Relations, Nov 1986-Dec 1986 (Box 56, Folder 16)
    - Public Relations, Jan 1987 (Box 56, Folder 17)
    - Public Relations, Feb 1987 (Box 56, Folder 18)
    - Public Relations, Mar 1987 (Box 56, Folder 19)
    - Public Relations, Mar 1987 (Box 56, Folder 20)
    - Public Relations, Apr 1987 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Public Relations, Apr 1987 (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - Public Relations, May 1987 (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - Public Relations, Jun 1987 (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - Public Relations, Jul 1987 (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - Public Relations, Aug 1987 (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - Public Relations, Sep 1987 (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - Public Relations, Oct 1987 (Box 57, Folder 8)
    - Public Relations, Nov 1987 (Box 57, Folder 9)
    - Public Relations, Dec 1987 (Box 57, Folder 10)
    - Public Relations, Jan 1988-Feb 1988 (Box 57, Folder 11)
    - Public Relations, Mar 1988 (Box 57, Folder 12)
    - Public Relations, Apr 1988 (Box 57, Folder 13)
    - Public Relations, May 1988-Jun 1988 (Box 57, Folder 14)
    - Public Relations, Jul 1988-Sep 1988 (Box 57, Folder 15)
    - Public Relations, Oct 1988-Dec 1988 (Box 57, Folder 16)
    - Public Relations, 1992 (Box 57, Folder 17)
    - Public Relations, 1993 (Box 57, Folder 18)
    - Public Relations, 1996 (Box 57, Folder 19)
    - Public Utilities Commission, 1986-1988 (Box 57, Folder 20)
    - Religious Objectors Policy, 1988 (Box 57, Folder 21)
    - Research, 1987 (Box 57, Folder 22)
    - Retiree Housing, 1986 (Box 57, Folder 23)
    - Savings Bonds Drive, 1992 (Box 57, Folder 24)
    - Service Employees International Union (SEIU), 1989-1990 (Box 57, Folder 25)
    - Social Security, 1986 (Box 57, Folder 26)
    - Special Commission on Employee Involvement and Ownership (MA), 1987 (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Speeches: Bahr, Morton, Jul 1985-Oct 1985 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - Speeches: Bahr, Morton, Nov 1985-Dec 1985 (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - Speeches: Bahr, Morton, Jan 1986-Feb 1986 (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - Speeches: Bahr, Morton, Mar 1986 (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - Speeches: Bahr, Morton, Apr 1986 (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - Speeches: Bahr, Morton, May 1986-Aug 1986 (Box 58, Folder 7)
    - Speeches: Bahr, Morton, Oct 1986 (Box 58, Folder 8)
    - Speeches: Bahr, Morton, Nov 1986-Dec 1986 (Box 58, Folder 9)
    - Speeches: Bahr, Morton, Jan 1987-Feb 1987 (Box 58, Folder 10)
    - Speeches: Bahr, Morton, Mar 1987 (Box 58, Folder 11)
    - Speeches: Bahr, Morton, Apr 1987 (Box 58, Folder 12)
    - Speeches: Bahr, Morton, May 1987 (Box 58, Folder 13)
    - Speeches: Bahr, Morton, Jun 1987 (Box 58, Folder 14)
    - Speeches: Bahr, Morton, Jul 1987 (Box 58, Folder 15)
    - Speeches: Bahr, Morton, Sep 1987 (Box 58, Folder 16)
    - Speeches: Bahr, Morton, Oct 1987-Dec 1987 (Box 58, Folder 17)
    - Speeches: Bahr, Morton, Jan 1988-Feb 1988 (Box 58, Folder 18)
    - Speeches: Bahr, Morton, Mar 1988 (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - Speeches: Bahr, Morton, Apr 1988-May 1988 (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - Speeches: Bahr, Morton, Jun 1988 (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - Speeches: Bahr, Morton, Jul 1988-Aug 1988 (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - Speeches: Bahr, Morton, Sep 1988 (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - Speeches: Bahr, Morton, Oct 1988-Nov 1988 (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - Speeches: Bahr, Morton, Index to, 1989 (Box 59, Folder 7)
    - Speeches: Bahr, Morton, Jan 1989-Mar 1989 (Box 59, Folder 8)
    - Speeches: Bahr, Morton, Apr 1989 (Box 59, Folder 9)
    - Speeches: Bahr, Morton, May 1989-Jun 1989 (Box 59, Folder 10)
    - Speeches: Bahr, Morton, Jul 1989 (Box 59, Folder 11)
    - Speeches: Bahr, Morton, Aug 1989-Sep 1989 (Box 59, Folder 12)
    - Speeches: Bahr, Morton, Oct 1989 (Box 59, Folder 13)
    - Speeches: Bahr, Morton, Nov 1989 (Box 59, Folder 14)
    - Speeches: Bahr, Morton, Jan 1990-Feb 1990 (Box 59, Folder 15)
    - Speeches: Bahr, Morton, Mar 1990-Apr 1990 (Box 59, Folder 16)
    - Speeches: Bahr, Morton, May 1990-Jun 1990 (Box 59, Folder 17)
    - Speeches: Bahr, Morton, Jul 1990-Dec 1990 (Box 59, Folder 18)
    - Speeches: Bahr, Morton, 1991 (Box 59, Folder 19)
    - Speeches: Bahr, Morton, 1992-1993 (Box 59, Folder 20)
    - Speeches: Bahr, Morton, 1994 (Box 59, Folder 21)
    - Speeches: Beaumont, Dina, 1984-1985 (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - Speeches: Carroll, John C., 1987-1988 (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - Speeches: Correspondence, 1986 (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - Speeches: Correspondence, 1987 (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - Speeches: Correspondence, 1988 (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - Speeches: Easterling, Barbara, 1986 (Box 60, Folder 6)